

Pavel Grigoryev

Front-end developer (React/Redux, Shopify)

Contacts

+375 (29) 393-53-77

Portfolio









Skills

- React
- Redux/Redux-Toolkit
- Redux Thunk
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Rest API / Axois
- Formik / React Hook Form
- Jest test / Snapshot test
- Storybook
- Material UI / Ant Design
- HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
- Shopify
- Liquid code
- Wordpress
- Webflow
- Git
- Jira
- Figma

Language

- English intermediate(in progress)
- Russian native
- Belarusian native

About Me

My name is Pavel. I'm a front-end developer with experience in creating websites on the Shopify platform and creating applications utilizing React/Redux and TypeScript. I like working with React for its flexibility and versatility, also I'm fond of the Shopify platform because I think it is the best product for creating e-commerce projects. In my free time, I watch videos and read articles about technologies that I want to learn such as Next.js, Hydrogen React, and Node.js. Also, I'm a big fan of bicycles and studying English.

Experience

Front-end developer

April 2022 - Present

Memorize App

Memorize is an application for memorizing information using cards. Register in the app and explore existing decks of cards on various topics or create your own. The application has the ability to create questions in the form of pictures.

Stack: React, Redux-toolkit, Redux-router-dom, Redux-thunk, Axios, TypeScript, MaterialUI, Formik.

TaskSpot App

TaskSpot is an application that allows you to create and manage to-do lists.

Stack: React, Redux-toolkit, Redux-router-dom, Redux-thunk, Axios, TypeScript, MaterialUI, Formik, Storybook, Jest test, Snapshot test.

Aspire App

Aspire is a social network where people can communicate with each other.

Stack: React, Redux, Redux-router-dom, Redux-thunk, Axios, TypeScript, React Hook Form, Jest test.

Online News Magazine

News magazine from scratch on the Wordpress platform with the collaboration of UX/UI designer. **Stack**: Wordpress, Webflow, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3.

Online E-Commerce Store

Migration of e-commerce store from the Shopify 1.0 to the Shopify 2.0 with the collaboration of UX/UI designer.

Stack: Shopify, Liquid code, Theme Kit, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3.

January 2022 - March 2022. MTN Haus

Online E-Commerce Stores

Creating web pages for e-commerce stores and their adaptation to the Shopify platform. Adaptation Shopify extensions in new e-commerce stores.

Stack: Shopify, Liquid code, Theme Kit, Shopify CLI, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3.

November 2021 - December 2021

Online E-Commerce Stores

Creating e-commerce stores on the Shopify platform.

Stack: Shopify, Liquid code, Theme Kit, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3.

Civil engineer

April 2012 - October 2021. ETM

I have been worked for a project company with 50 employees as a lead civil engineer.

Education

2022 - 2023. IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end developer (React/Redux, TypeScript)

2022. ItGid.info: "JavaScript v2.0"

Front-end developer (JavaScript)

2021. FREEMOTE: The Freelance Developer Bootcamp

Front-end developer (Shopify, Liquid code, HTML/CSS/JS)